{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Mist Cooling System Repair Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/40295/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40295,"taskName":"Outdoor Mist Cooling System - Service or Repair","taskDescription":"Service an Outdoor Mist Cooling System","xmTaskDescriptor":"Mist Cooling System Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":172,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Airconditioning Outdoor Mist air airconditioners","textMessagingName":"Repr Mist System","rolloverLongDesc":"Used in hot parts of the country. Jets spray a barely noticeable spray into the air. The evaporation draws heat out of the air creating an area of relative coolness. Also called outdoor air conditioning.","rolloverShortDesc":"Uses mist to cool outdoor patios.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Service an Outdoor Mist Cooling System.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Mist Cooling System Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Fix Outdoor Mist System","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":47,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Mist System Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Outdoor Mist Cooling System - Service or Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Mist Cooling System Project","urlName":"Outdoor-Mist-Cooling-System-Service-or-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Mist Cooling System Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Outdoor,Mist,air,exterior,mister,misting,evaporative,cool,conditioning,ac,","emcCategoryOid":-12002,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":595,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40295/":{"taskOID":40295,"originalTaskOID":40295,"setID":595,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4756,"questionDisplayText":"Installation Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the misting system installed? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4496,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Outside patio area for cooling","answerDisplayText":"Outside patio area for cooling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4497,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Outside patio area for misting plants","answerDisplayText":"Outside patio area for misting plants","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":842,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Around pool, spa, gazebo","answerDisplayText":"Around pool, spa, gazebo","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3404,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Kennel, barn etc. to cool animals","answerDisplayText":"Kennel, barn etc. to cool animals","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2639,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Freestanding greenhouse","answerDisplayText":"Freestanding greenhouse","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3227,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Inside home for greenhouse","answerDisplayText":"Inside home for greenhouse","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3228,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Inside home for terrarium","answerDisplayText":"Inside home for terrarium","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4758,"questionDisplayText":"Problem Analysis","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the problem? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10106,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Noise, but no mist","answerDisplayText":"Noise, but no mist","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10107,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Leaks/drips","answerDisplayText":"Leaks/drips","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10108,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Won't go on and off properly","answerDisplayText":"Won't go on and off properly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10109,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Nozzles need replacing","answerDisplayText":"Nozzles need replacing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10110,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Need to extend misting area","answerDisplayText":"Need to extend misting area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10111,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Needs increased pressure","answerDisplayText":"Needs increased pressure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10112,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"System needs upgrading","answerDisplayText":"System needs upgrading","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10113,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Preventative Maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Preventative Maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6935,"questionDisplayText":"Square footage of misted area","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the approximate square footage of the misting area?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10102,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 100 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"Less than 100 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10103,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"100 - 500 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"100 - 500 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10104,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"500 - 1000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"500 - 1000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10105,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 1000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"More than 1000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4756,"questionDisplayText":"Installation Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the misting system installed? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4496,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Outside patio area for cooling","answerDisplayText":"Outside patio area for cooling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4497,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Outside patio area for misting plants","answerDisplayText":"Outside patio area for misting plants","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":842,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Around pool, spa, gazebo","answerDisplayText":"Around pool, spa, gazebo","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3404,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Kennel, barn etc. to cool animals","answerDisplayText":"Kennel, barn etc. to cool animals","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2639,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Freestanding greenhouse","answerDisplayText":"Freestanding greenhouse","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3227,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Inside home for greenhouse","answerDisplayText":"Inside home for greenhouse","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3228,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Inside home for terrarium","answerDisplayText":"Inside home for terrarium","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4496,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Outside patio area for cooling","answerDisplayText":"Outside patio area for cooling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4497,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Outside patio area for misting plants","answerDisplayText":"Outside patio area for misting plants","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":842,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Around pool, spa, gazebo","answerDisplayText":"Around pool, spa, gazebo","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3404,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Kennel, barn etc. to cool animals","answerDisplayText":"Kennel, barn etc. to cool animals","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2639,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Freestanding greenhouse","answerDisplayText":"Freestanding greenhouse","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3227,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Inside home for greenhouse","answerDisplayText":"Inside home for greenhouse","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3228,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Inside home for terrarium","answerDisplayText":"Inside home for terrarium","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4758,"questionDisplayText":"Problem Analysis","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the problem? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10106,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Noise, but no mist","answerDisplayText":"Noise, but no mist","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10107,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Leaks/drips","answerDisplayText":"Leaks/drips","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10108,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Won't go on and off properly","answerDisplayText":"Won't go on and off properly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10109,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Nozzles need replacing","answerDisplayText":"Nozzles need replacing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10110,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Need to extend misting area","answerDisplayText":"Need to extend misting area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10111,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Needs increased pressure","answerDisplayText":"Needs increased pressure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10112,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"System needs upgrading","answerDisplayText":"System needs upgrading","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10113,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Preventative Maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Preventative Maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10106,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Noise, but no mist","answerDisplayText":"Noise, but no mist","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10107,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Leaks/drips","answerDisplayText":"Leaks/drips","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10108,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Won't go on and off properly","answerDisplayText":"Won't go on and off properly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10109,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Nozzles need replacing","answerDisplayText":"Nozzles need replacing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10110,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Need to extend misting area","answerDisplayText":"Need to extend misting area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10111,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Needs increased pressure","answerDisplayText":"Needs increased pressure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10112,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"System needs upgrading","answerDisplayText":"System needs upgrading","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10113,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Preventative Maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Preventative Maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6935,"questionDisplayText":"Square footage of misted area","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the approximate square footage of the misting area?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10102,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 100 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"Less than 100 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10103,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"100 - 500 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"100 - 500 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10104,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"500 - 1000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"500 - 1000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10105,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 1000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"More than 1000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10102,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 100 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"Less than 100 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10103,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"100 - 500 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"100 - 500 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10104,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"500 - 1000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"500 - 1000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10105,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 1000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"More than 1000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}